<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Chris Hong</title><link>https://chrishong.us/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Hong</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Hero image by Daniel Ellis 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 08:25:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chrishong.us/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ignorance</title><link>https://chrishong.us/post/being_civilized/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 08:25:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://chrishong.us/post/being_civilized/</guid><description>This morning I was taking a run around the block of our parent&amp;rsquo;s home. I&amp;rsquo;m a terrible runner, I just do it for my health and destressing. It also gives me an opportunity to go outside.
The weather was cloudy and the air cool and humid. I was going on my casual run with my wireless earbuds on listening to music by Daughtry from the 2000s, when I noticed a little something.</description></item><item><title>Workplace Survival Guide</title><link>https://chrishong.us/post/workplace_survival_guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 09:49:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://chrishong.us/post/workplace_survival_guide/</guid><description>I wanted to make this post because we currently live in a world in which a majority of people need to submit themselves to a 40 to 80 hour a week job in a tyrannical organization, but frankly there is very little good advice about how to navigate the working world. Here I present a short essay on what I believe to be the most valuable lessons I learned on my first coroporate job out of college at a large multinational defense contractor.</description></item><item><title>iFly</title><link>https://chrishong.us/post/ifly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 12:39:55 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://chrishong.us/post/ifly/</guid><description>Year 2050
Good afternoon and welcome aboard to Eagle airlines! This is your captain speaking. The duration of this flight will be approximately seven hours from Shanghai to New York. A special welcome to our first class passengers, we have a full course meal from our very own Michelin starred chef, a unique collection of exclusive alcohols to ease your mind, and a porthole where you can view with your own eyes the natural splendor of the Himalayan mountains as we pass over.</description></item></channel></rss>